So the task, the session that you just created was a vanilla
Claude or Codex session.
But we also have a concept of Unmute Agent.
So Unmute Agent is a specialized session that we create
and it has these tools and some capabilities
that allows it to find tasks,
allows to create new tasks and continue working on
existing tasks for you.
So think of it like a task manager or a session manager.
Let's say you were working on something a couple of days back
and you want to start working on it again.
So what you could do is you can just unmute yourself.
You can talk to Unmute Agent and you can tell it, hey, let's start,
let's continue working on the landing page.
That's it.
That's the, you know,
simplest of a request that you have to make to the Unmute Agent.
What it will do is it will find the right session
that you are already working on and it will resume that session.
It will make sure that it has the right set of
contexts and you can just proceed from there.
So it's like a sessions manager.
It's really useful and you don't have to think about what session you
were, you were working on earlier.
You don't have to look for those sessions.
At the same time.
You can say, hey, can you do this,
can you do this task A again for this particular thing?
And it'll just make sure to find the right set of
context from your past session.
Just bring that in front of you so you don't have to think about
or worry about
resuming a previous session, finding the right session, etc.
So it's a really good, it's a really important feature.
And yeah, think of it like a task manager.
What you have to do is double tap the Right Command key to talk to
Unmute Agent
and just say out loud whatever you want to say.
You can say the follow up message as shown here to test it
and once done tap the Right Command key again and
that will submit a Unmute Agent request.
it will also pop up in a notch.
So you can just tap on the notch and it will just show Unmute
Agent specific task or Unmute Agent specific chat box.
So that's a chat of yours and the Unmute Agent.
And once the Unmute Agent is done with the follow up,
it will most likely give you a link
and you can tap that link and it will open the right session.
So it's a really cool feature.
You can just try it out.